Brecken……我不希望你吃里面的任何东西，明白吗?
Brecken... I don't want you eating anything you find in there, you understand me?
我不管它是什么。
I don't care what it is.
不管它是什么。
Don't care what it is.
啊…妈妈!妈妈!
Ah... Mum! Mum!
——不!不!
- No! No!
不!不,不!
No! No, no!
是吗?
Yes?
是的，还是Djuna。
Yes, it's still Djuna.
现在你已经确认了电话号码。
Now you've confirmed the phone number.
我要你告诉朗如果他有兴趣去捡那个被他称为儿子的生物的尸体是的，我是说布雷肯。
I want you to tell Lang that if he's interested in picking up the corpse of that creature he calls his son-- Yes, yes, I mean the Brecken thing.
所以，你告诉他到我给你的地址来。
So, you tell him to come to the address I gave you.
它会在这里，而我却不在。
It will be here, and I won't be.
我的孩子，孩子，孩子。
Oh, my boy, boy, boy.
我的孩子。哦,我的孩子。
My boy. Oh, my boy.
扫罗。
Saul.
索尔，亲爱的，你能醒醒吗?
Saul, darling, can you wake up?
这里是谁?
Who's here?
这只是我。
It's just me.
这是任性。
It's Caprice.
你睡了吗?
Did you sleep?
我觉得这……床需要新的软件。
I think this... bed needs new software.
它不会再预见我的痛苦了。
It's not anticipating my pain anymore.
它不能让我正常转动。
It's not turning me properly.
-是的，我听到了
- Yes, I heard you.
-一个不眠之夜。
- A sleepless night.
我马上给LifeFormWare打电话。
I will call LifeFormWare right away.
他们通常很有反应。
They're usually very responsive.
——还有什么?还有什么?
- What else? What else?
-测试做了一整晚，今天早上就做好了。
- The tests cooked all night and were ready this morning.
你的血液中有一种新的激素。
There is a new hormone in your bloodstream.
啊…太好了。
Ah... Great.
它是关于时间。
It's about time.
我以为我已经筋疲力尽了。
I thought I was all tapped out.
枯竭。
Dried up.
-你总是这么想，你总是错的。
- You always think that, and you're always wrong.
-总有一天我会说对的
- One day, I'll be right.
不是今天。
Not today.
现在还没吃早饭呢。
It's still before breakfast.
你看到了什么?
What do you see?
我能感觉到你在里面拖东西。
I can feel you pulling things around in there.
-好像是一种小的内分泌腺，肾上腺大小。
- It seems to be some small sort of, uh, endocrine gland, about the size of an adrenal gland.
小。
Small.
这是令人失望的。这不是很戏剧化。
That's disappointing. It's not very dramatic.
-这是一个从未见过的全新器官。
- It's a brand new organ Never before seen.
是的。
Yeah.
-它在工作。
- And it's functioning.
你能感觉到吗?
Can you feel it?
新激素?
That new hormone?
是的。
Yeah.
哦,LifeFormWare。
Oh, LifeFormWare.
LifeFormWare吗?
LifeFormWare?
是的。
Yeah.
痛苦是不同的。
The pain is different.
这可能就是我床上的电脑出问题的原因。
That's probably why my bed's computer's having trouble.
这个新器官，它在转移我的疼痛中枢。
This new organ, it's, uh, it's shifting my pain centres.
-是好是坏?
- For better or worse?
-到目前为止，只是不同而已。
- So far, just different.
美术进展如何?
How's the artwork progressing?
这是一个很滑的表面。
It's a slippery surface.
用墨水很难精确。
Hard to be precise with the ink.
嗯……为什么不做一些看起来像纹身的东西呢?
Huh... Why not do something that really looks like a tattoo?
一颗心，一个锚，“妈妈”?
A heart, an anchor, "Mother"?
-那会很好玩的。
- That would be playful.
但书记官处坚持“独特的自我参照”。
But the Registry insists on "uniquely self-referential."
啊,注册表。
Ah, the Registry.
当然可以。
Of course.
扫罗紧张。
Saul Tenser.
反复无常。
Caprice.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
所以你。
So you are.
受欢迎的。
Welcome.
对了，我叫威佩特。
I'm Wippet, by the way.
哇,嗯…-这是我们的荣幸，不是吗，蒂姆林?
Wow, um... - This is a real treat and a privilege for us, isn't it, Timlin?
这是Timlin。
That's Timlin.
这不是很壮观，对吧，但这是国家器官登记中心，我们的设备很齐全，不是吗，蒂姆林?
This isn't very grand, is it, but this is the National Organ Registry nonetheless, and we're fully equipped, aren't we, Timlin?
现在这些都是秘密，因为我们是正义NVU的一员，但我们会做好准备，在不可避免的时候公开。
Um, it's all secret stuff now because we're part of the NVU of Justice, but we'll be ready to break out and go public when the time inevitably comes.
NVU吗?
NVU?
新的副单位。
New Vice Unit.
没有什么犯罪比得上现在。
No crime like the present.
-抱歉，我们对程序有点困惑。
- Sorry, we're a little confused about procedure.
这是我们第一次。
This is our first time.
嗯。
Hm.
但是你从安全的角度了解器官登记的必要性吗?
But you understand the necessity of organ registration from a security standpoint?
我们知道人体正在发生变化。
We understand human bodies are changing.
我很清楚这一点。
I know this quite well.
嗯…显然，这是世界各国政府所关心的问题。
Um... And, apparently, this is of some concern to the governments of the world.
人类的身体,是的。
Human bodies, yes.
“人”是关键字。
"Human" is the operative word.
人类进化是问题所在。
Human evolution is the concern.
它出了问题。
That it's going wrong.
它是……不受控制的,这是……起义的。
That it's... uncontrolled, it's... insurrectional.
它可能会把我们引向不好的地方。
It might lead us to a bad place.
比如，看看疼痛阈值发生了什么变化。
Look what's happened to the pain thresholds, for instance.
现在世界变得更加危险，因为疼痛几乎消失了。
The world is a much more dangerous place now that p-p-pain has all but disappeared.
只有少数幸运儿在睡眠中经历疼痛有什么好处呢?
What good is it that only a lucky handful of us experience pain in our sleep?
疼痛是有作用的。
Pain has a function.
这是一个我们已经没有的预警系统，这是怎么发生的，这意味着什么?
It is a warning system that we don't have anymore, and how did this happen, what does this mean?
或者感染呢?
Or, or what about infections?
感染?他们怎么了?
Infections? What happened to them?
现在没人洗手了。
Nobody washes their hands anymore.
那是什么，那个新的时尚，叫什么来着?桌面手术?
What is it- what is that new, uh, fad, uh, what do they call it? Desktop surgery?
在公共场合!
In public!
这是令人厌恶的。
It's repulsive.
——嗯…我们的记录显示多年来你一直在随机制造新奇的身体器官，但你一直在移除它们。
- Um... Our records indicate that you've been producing random and novel bodily organs for some years, but that you've had them consistently removed.
谁不想呢?
Who wouldn't?
-你会很惊讶的。
- You'd be surprised.
-我们会很惊讶。
- We would be surprised.
它们基本上是肿瘤，对吧?
They're basically tumours, right?
谁会想要它们呢?
Who would want to keep them?
他们会杀了你的。
They could kill you.
你们俩是什么关系?
- What is the relationship between you two?
-我切除这些肿瘤是我们表演的一部分。
- I remove these tumours as part of our performance.
我们是行为艺术家。
We are performance artists.
我们一起执行。
We perform together.
嗯。
Hm.
你有资格做手术吗?
And you're qualified to perform surgery?
-就像威佩特先生说的，现在每个人都有资格做手术。
- Well, as Mr. Wippet was saying, everybody's qualified to perform surgery these days.
如果同意是合法的，那就真的没有问题了。
- If consent is legally given, there is really no- no issue there.
嗯。
Hm.
我说的是你们的工作关系。
I was speaking of your professional relationship.
你不会想杀了你的表演搭档吧?
You wouldn't want to kill your performance partner, would you?
你永远不会知道的。
You never know.
我们的演出中有很多即兴表演。
There's a lot of improvisation in our shows.
阻止它。
Stop it.
嗯。
Hm.
我们是在索尔执行任务时认识的。
- We met when Saul was cut up on duty.
我曾是第一总医院的创伤外科医生。
I was a trauma surgeon at First General.
我们释放了彼此的潜能。
We unleashed things in each other.
我们都改变了，离开了我们的职业。
We both changed, left our professions.
现在我们就是这样了。
And now we are what we are.
哦。
Oh.
你们是明星，这就是你们。
You're stars, that's what you are.
天啊，现在每个人都想成为行为艺术家。
Gosh, everyone wants to be a performance artist these days.
-现在很流行，但是…不是每个人都能做的。
- It's all the rage, but... not everyone can do it.
好吧,然后……
Well, then...
注册?
Registration?
哦,我的。
Oh, my.
哦，它是如此美丽!
Oh, it is so beautiful!
-我的角度看不太清楚。
- I can't quite see it from my angle.
你能从你所在的地方把它捡起来吗?
Can you pick it up from where you are?
-哦,是的。这很清楚没办法。
- Oh, yes. It's-it's very clear.
哦,天哪!
Oh, gosh!
这是一个华丽的，我甚至可以说，纹身者艺术的感性的例子。
It is a gorgeous, I might even say, sensual example of the registration tatooist's art.
-你为什么不告诉我们注册纹身是什么?
- Why don't you tell us what a registration tattoo is?
嗯,嗯……我们国家器官登记处刚刚制定了一项新政策，即在新器官或特发性器官上纹身，即在功能未知的新器官上纹身，以便对它们进行登记和跟踪。
Well, um... ... we here at the National Organ Registry have just instituted a new policy of tattooing novel organs, or idiopathic organs, that is, new organs whose function is unknown,so that they can be registered and kept track of.
嗯，我们的恐惧是……这些新器官中的一些可能会在基因上建立起来，然后从父母传给孩子，严格地说，孩子就不再是人类了。
Um, our fear is... that some of these neo-organs might establish themselves genetically, and then be passed down from parents to children, who would then no longer be, strictly speaking, human.
至少在传统意义上是这样。
At least, in the classical sense.
我们对注册纹身的概念很大程度上受到了Saul Tenser的行为艺术的启发。
Our concept of the registration tattoo was largely inspired by the performance art of Saul Tenser.
-哦，我很抱歉，但这里禁止录音。
- Oh, I'm so sorry, but it's forbidden to record in here.
-哦，对，对。她是对的。
- Oh, right, right. She's right.
-我在想我们可以用它来表演。
- I was thinking we could use it for our performance.
我们记录最私密的事情。
We record the most intimate things.
-对不起，这是违法的。
- I'm sorry, but it is illegal.
这个部门还不存在。
This department does not yet exist.
-对，如果它不存在，我想，那就不可能录音。
- Right, if it doesn't exist, then, I guess, it's impossible to make a recording.
——对不起。
- Sorry.
太糟糕了。
Too bad.
我觉得你不该邀请登记处的那两个变态来参加我们的节目。
I don't think you should have invited those two creeps from the registry to our show.
——为什么不呢?
- Why not?
为什么不让他们站在我们这边?
Why not get 'em on our side?
我不相信他们。
I don't trust them.
那个女人，蒂姆林，她…尤其令人毛骨悚然。
The woman, Timlin, she's, uh... especially creepy.
嗯。
Hm.
我认为她相当迷人。
I thought she was rather attractive.
以官僚主义的方式。
In a... bureaucratic way.
嗯。
Hm.
LifeFormWare的技术人员在这里。
The LifeFormWare technicians are here.
他们需要看到你躺在床上。
They need to see you in your bed.
-我对纹身有点不高兴。
- I'm a little upset about the tattoo.
哦?
Oh?
喧闹的。
Rambunctious.
我就是这么叫的。
That's what I'd call it.
-这是专业术语吗?
- That's a technical term?
紧张。;呃。
TENSER.; Uh.
-它接管了器官本身的形状。
- It takes over the form, the shape of the organ itself.
从某种意义上说，它真的主导了它，重塑了它。
It really, in a sense, dominates it, reshapes it.
它不仅仅是寄生的，尽管我认为，在某种意义上，它也是。
It's not just parasitic, although I suppose, in a sense, it is that too.
它似乎剥夺了器官的意义。
It seems to take meaning away from the organ.
可以这么说，他把意义的过程当作自己的过程。
Takes the process of meaning for itself, so to speak.
-你最好上床睡觉。
- You'd really better get into bed.
在那里,在那里。
There, there.
你很快就会舒服的。
You'll be comfortable again soon.
OrchidBed是我们线床的顶部。
OrchidBed is our top of the line bed.
一旦我们纠正了由你的…荷尔蒙失调，你会浮起来。
Once we correct the misalignment caused by your... hormonal imbalance, you'll be floating.
——嗯。
- Huh.
-对吧，Berst?
- Isn't that right, Berst?
——嗯。
- Uh-uh.
是的，这些东西基本上是防弹的。
Yeah, these things are basically bulletproof.
这张床喜欢你的身材，张瑟先生。
This bed loves your body, Mr. Tenser.
它是如此灵活，如此适应你疼痛中枢的每一个变化，这是一件美丽的事情。
It is so flexible, so attuned to every shift of your pain centres, it's a beautiful thing to behold.
我看到你这里有我们几个小队的人-是吗?-嗯嗯。
I see you actually have several of our units here, - don't you? - Mm-hm.
-兰花床，早餐椅，这些可能也需要一些调整。
- The OrchidBed Bed, the BreakFaster Chair, that'll probably need some adjustment as well.
我们可以……下载你的OrchidBed坐标到BreakFaster，调整EatWare参数，我们应该会非常接近。
We can... download your OrchidBed co-ordinates into the BreakFaster, tweak the EatWare parameters, and we should be very close.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
路由器。
Router.
它是什么?
What is it?
-坦瑟先生在这里有一个萨克小队。
- Mr. Tenser has a Sark unit here.
是的。
Yes.
他确实。
He really does.
萨克号验尸舱是我们做过的最好的验尸舱之一。它是美丽的。
- The Sark autopsy module was one of the best units we ever made. It's gorgeous.
他们是传奇。
They're legendary.
如此复杂。
So complex.
所以微妙。
So subtle.
-你用过这个吗?
- Do you ever work on one of these?
-他们在我们的时代之前就停止制造了。
- They stopped making them before our time.
我从没见过真人。
I've never seen one in the flesh before.
——他们是传奇。
- They're legendary.
-你用它做什么?
- What do you use it for?
你不是做尸检的吧?
You're not in the autopsy business, are you?
-这是我的画笔。
- It's my paint brush.
嗯。
Hm.
我的天啊，看看这个。
Mm, oh, my God, look at this thing.
不,你不能。
No, you can't.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
-没那么小。
- It's not that small.
-实际上相当大。
- Quite big, actually.
嗯。
Hm.
你介意我问你一些私人问题吗?
- Do you mind if I ask you something intimate?
嗨。
Hi.
不,请便。
No, go ahead.
-手术就是做爱，对吧?
- That surgery is sex, isn't it?
是吗?
Is it?
嗯。
Hm.
你知道的。
You know it is.
手术是新的性爱。
Surgery is the new sex.
嗯。
Hm.
一定要有新的性爱吗?
Does there have to be new sex?
是的。
Yes.
是的,它是。
Yes, it's time.
当我看着卡普瑞斯切入你的时候，我想…
When I was watching Caprice cut into you, I wanted...
是吗?
Yes?
-我想让你切入我。
- I wanted you to be cutting into me.
那时我就知道了。
That's when I knew.
嗯。
Hm.
——嗯?
- Hm?
-那是怎么回事?
- What was that all about?
-又一次顿悟。
- Just another epiphany.
艺术再次获得胜利。
Art triumphs once again.
嗯。
Hm.
-他的身体需求是微妙的，而且在不断变化。
- His body needs are subtle and they're constantly shifting.
我和丹尼·鲁特都觉得，坦瑟这个账户会让我们整个组织进入一个全新的，令人振奋的领域。
We feel, Danny Router and I do, that the Tenser account will force our entire organization into new, exhilarating territory.
扫罗紧张是……内心风景的艺术家。
Saul Tenser is... an artist of the inner landscape.
艺术创作常常与疼痛联系在一起，而疼痛，正如我们所知，总是与睡眠联系在一起。
Creation of art is often associated with pain, and pain, as we know, is always associated with sleep.
我们在LifeFormWare专门操纵和调节艺术家的痛苦，对我们来说，Saul Tenser是最大的挑战，如此亲密和涉及他的艺术，和他的痛苦的性质。
We at LifeFormWare specialize in manipulating and modulating the pain of artists, and, to us, Saul Tenser is the greatest challenge, so intimate and involving in his art, and the nature of his pain.
睡个好觉是…当你是一个寻求痛苦的艺术家时，很难定义。
A good night's sleep is a... hard thing to define when you're an artist and you seek pain.
嗯。
Hm.
坐
Sit down.
我是侦探应付。
I'm Detective Cope.
我是新Vice的。
I'm with New Vice.
和你是谁?
And you are?
——Wippet。——Timlin。
- Wippet. - Timlin.
嗯,是的,很好。
Hm, yes, good.
你最近和行为艺术家索尔·坦瑟有来往吗?
Have you had recent dealings with the performance artist, Saul Tenser?
是的。
Yes.
-你有他开发和切除的所有新器官的文件夹吗?
- And you have a portfolio of all the neo-organs which he has developed and removed?
-他捐赠给我们的
- He donated it to us.
他是第一个对自己内心的创作进行记录和存档的人。
He was the first to undertake the logging, the archiving, of his inner creations.
我们称之为张力组织学。
We call it the Tenser Organography.
对他来说，这是一件艺术的事情，一个艺术家想要系统化地记录他的艺术。
For him, it was an art thing, an artist wanting a systematized record of his art.
-但是，对我们来说，它引发了对流动的意识，对许多人正在秘密经历的这些自发生长的意义的意识。
- But, for us, it triggered an awareness of the flow, the significance of these spontaneous growths which many people were experiencing in secret.
所以，现在，我们实际上要求对这些增长进行合法登记。
So, now, we have actually required the legal registering of these growths.
-注册一个真正的，新的…索尔紧张内部器官…-这就像发现一种新的动物物种。
- The registering of a genuine, new... Saul Tenser internal organ... - It's like discovering a new species of animal.
更像是发现了一个新的毕加索。
Well, more like discovering a new Picasso.
-肿瘤生长怎么会被认为是艺术?
- How can a tumorous growth be considered art?
一切艺术的基础——情感的塑造、哲学的理解在哪里?
Where is the emotional shaping, the philosophical understanding, which is basic to all art?
看……
Look...
我腹部有个肿块。
I have a lump on my abdomen.
你看到了吗?
You see it?
毕加索?
Picasso?
杜尚吗?
Duchamp?
弗朗西斯·培根,可能吗?
Francis Bacon, perhaps?
我是艺术家吗?
Am I an artist?
-他对自己的身体进行反叛并控制它。
- He takes the rebellion of his own body and seizes control of it.
塑造它，纹身，展示它，用它创造戏剧。
Shapes it, tattoos it, displays it, creates theatre out of it.
它有意义，非常有力的意义，而且……很多很多人对此做出了回应。
It has meaning, very potent meaning, and... many, many people respond to it.
——是的。
- Yes.
纹身吗?
Tattoos it?
我们开始吧。
Here we go.
嗯。
Hm.
你看到了什么?
You see?
从一开始，在他遇到卡布里斯之后，他所有的新器官都在他体内纹上了。
See, right from the beginning, after he met Caprice, all his neo-organs were tattooed while they were still inside his body.
-反复无常是他的情人?
- Caprice is his lover?
-反复无常是他的表演搭档。
- Caprice is his performance partner.
她做纹身。
She does the tattoos.
和手术。
And the surgery.
嗯。
Hm.
在我看来，卡布里斯就是艺术家。
Looks to me as though Caprice is the artist.
坦瑟只是个被美化过的器官捐赠者。
Tenser is just a glorified organ donor.
-有表演。
- Well, there are the performances.
然后，然后，就有了意志的问题。
And, then-then, there is the question of will.
会吗?
Will?
是的。
Yes.
我们相信，在某种程度上，也许是潜意识，索尔·坦瑟会让这些新器官生长。
We believe, that on a certain level, perhaps a subconscious one, Saul Tenser wills these new organs to grow.
所以…
So...
嗯，你真的应该去看看你腹部的肿块。
Hm, you really ought to get that lump on your abdomen looked at.
扫罗?
Saul?
索尔，亲爱的，你能醒醒吗?
Saul, darling, can you wake up?
你的床上写着你在研究新东西。
Your bed says that you're working on something new.
这是对的吗?
Can that be right?
这么快?
So soon?
-床很安静。
- The bed is very quiet.
这张床永远不会出错。
The bed is never wrong.
问问我们在LifeFormWare的朋友就知道了。
Just ask our friends at LifeFormWare.
-这是我们该担心的吗?
- Is this something we should worry about?
增长的间隔似乎正在缩短。
The interval between growths seems to be closing up.
-我觉得很有创意。
- I'm feeling very creative.
我猜。
I guess.
我们得快点切了。
We'll just have to start cutting faster.
-是时候停止约会了。
- It is time to stop seeing.
是时候停止说话了。
It is time to stop speaking.
是时候倾听了。
It is time to listen.
-我不喜欢耳朵。
- I don't like the ears.
什么?
What?
的耳朵。
The ears.
它们很可爱，很引人注目，但一千只耳朵可不是什么好设计。
They're cute, they're striking, but a thousand ears is not good design.
环绕声吗?
Surround sound?
多余的耳朵根本不管用。
The extra ears don't even work.
它们只是作秀而已。
They're just for show.
-你怎么知道?
- How do you know?
我是阿德里安娜摇篮。
I'm Adrienne Berceau.
我是Klinek的生物形态学协调员。
I'm Klinek's Biomorphology Coordinator.
别告诉他是我说的，他跳舞比概念艺术更在行。
Don't tell him I said this, but he's better with the dancing than he is with the conceptual art.
你在研究什么新东西吗，坦瑟先生?
Are you working on anything new, Mr. Tenser?
-我真的不知道我什么时候在做新东西。
- I never really know when I'm working on something new.
这似乎不是我能决定的。
It doesn't seem to be my decision.
如果是呢?
What if it is?
如果它是吗?
If it is?
-内在美的创造不可能是偶然的。
- The creation of inner beauty cannot be an accident.
原谅我引用了你和你的节目。
Forgive me for quoting you and your show.
你听说过纳萨蒂尔医生吗?
Have you heard of Dr. Nasatir?
不。
No.
-你应该去拜访他。
- You should pay him a visit.
内在美是他的专长，也是你的专长。
Inner beauty is his specialty, as it is yours.
我已经为你预约了。
I've booked you an appointment.
去写在这里的地址。
Go to the address written here.
-关于医疗问题的咨询?
- A consultation about a medical problem?
-关于政治问题的咨询。
- A consultation about a political problem.
-我有个想法。
- I have a concept for you.
是吗?
Yeah?
是的,是的。
Yeah, yeah.
当我看到你在你的节目中使用萨克小队时，我就想到了。
It came to me when I saw you use a Sark unit as part of your show.
萨克号最初是一个解剖舱。
The Sark was originally an autopsy module.
你知道吗?
Did you know that?
我知道。
I knew that.
-你有没有想过用它来做真正的尸检?
- Have you ever thought about using it for a real autopsy?
作为你节目的一部分?
As part of your show?
进行尸检?
Perform an autopsy?
-在尸体上。嗯嗯。
- On a corpse. Mm-hm.
我有一具尸体给你。
I have a corpse for you.
这是一具非常特别的尸体。
It's a very special corpse.
你可以在尸体上做活体解剖。
You could do a live autopsy on a dead body.
而且会有惊喜。我保证会有惊喜的。
And there would be surprises. I can guarantee a few surprises.
-你说的是什么尸体?
- What corpse are you talking about?
我的儿子。
My son.
八岁。
Eight years old.
-为什么他是一具尸体?
- Why is he a corpse?
-他母亲杀了他。不会是…是演出的好原料吗?
- His mother murdered him. Wouldn't that be... good raw material for a performance?
-你有你儿子的尸体?
- You have the body of your son?
-是的，我当然有我儿子的尸体
- Yes, of course I have the body of my son.
他是我的儿子。
He's my son.
哇。
Wow.
是的,我知道。
Yeah, I know.
我是说，你有多激进?
I mean, how radical are you?
嗯?
Hm?
你害怕一点点情绪吗?
Are you afraid of a little emotion?
-我什么都怕。
- I'm afraid of everything.
今天喉咙的问题很严重。
The throat thing is very severe today.
我打不开。
I can't open it.
这是怎么呢
What's going on?
我不确定。
I am not sure.
-你昨天睡了很长时间。
- You were out for a very long time yesterday.
是的。
Yeah.
不是我过敏。
It's not my allergies.
事实上，它们并没有打扰到我。
In fact, they're not bothering me.
——这是奇怪的。
- It's strange.
-你不舒服吗?
- Are you in discomfort?
不,这是一个…引人注目的丰满。
No, it's a... compelling fullness.
这种感觉还不错。
Not a completely bad feeling.
-至少不是…无趣的。
- At least not... uninteresting.
我去看了Klinek。
I went to see the Klinek.
它怎么样?
How was it?
——一般。
- The usual.
-挤满了人。
- It was packed.
嫉妒?
Jealous?
当然可以。
Of course.
-但不是这样的。
- But that's not it.
我见过一个人…
I met this guy...
-在街上。
- On the street.
他有一个表演的想法。
He had an idea for a show.
所以，我就是那男孩的尸体。
So, I'm the boy's corpse.
我们得改装一下萨克号。
We'll have to modify the Sark.
嗯。
Hm.
-把它变回一个解剖模块。
- Convert it back into an autopsy module.
-我不知道关于侮辱人类遗体的法律在哪里。
- I don't know where the law is on acts degrading to human remains.
我们要做得出格才值得。
We'll have to be outrageous to make it worthwhile.
我们必须深入。
We have to go deep.
我不确定我们要怎么从内在美的角度出发。
I'm not sure how we'd play the inner beauty angle.
这个叫Dotrice的家伙说会有惊喜——哦。
This guy, Dotrice, he said there'd be surprises... - Oops.
——哦。——对不起。
- Oh. - Sorry.
-那是机器在说话。
- That was the machinery talking.
-那是你说的
- That was you talking.
继续。
Keep going.
真的吗?
Really?
到目前为止…很好。
So far... so good.
哦……
Oh...
哦……哦!哦……
Oh... Oh! Oh...
-你可以进入下一场演出。
- You could be on the inside for the next show.
也许吧。
Maybe.
但也许这只是为了我们。
But maybe this is just for us.
你感觉怎么样?
How are you feeling?
你是什么意思?
What do you mean?
-有什么好吃的吗?
- Got anything cooking in there?
嗯。
Huh.
你的想象力在加班加点地工作。
Your imagination's working overtime.
-我只是想看看你的作品集
- I just got to see your portfolio.
你非常高产。
You are very prolific.
我完全不知道。
I had no idea.
一定很累吧?
It must be exhausting, uh?
-没有它我也能活。
- I could live without it.
-听着，照亮我。
- Listen, illuminate me.
为什么索尔·坦瑟要做卧底?
Why is Saul Tenser doing undercover?
我是说，你似乎对人体艺术很感兴趣。
I mean, you seem to be pretty deep into that body-art stuff.
嗯…
Well...
关于身体艺术，我想说的是我不喜欢身体上发生的事情。
What I'm saying with that body-art stuff is that I don't like what's happening with the body.
特别是我的身体发生了什么，这就是为什么我一直在切割它。
In particular, what's happening with my body, which is why I keep cutting it up.
-你的搭档卡普瑞斯，她对此一无所知?
- Your partner, Caprice, she's in the dark about this?
被子下面的那个?
The under the covers?
是的。
Yeah.
——完全?-是的。
- Totally? - Yeah.
-她不能读懂你的内心?
- She can't read your insides?
没有任何卧底的痕迹吗?
There aren't any traces there that say undercover stoolie?
-你真的很有想象力。
- You really are imaginative.
-你给我带了什么?
- What have you got for me?
Nasatir博士。
Dr. Nasatir.
整容手术。
Cosmetic surgery.
-有人在Klinek展会上联系我。
- Someone contacted me at the Klinek show.
-我听说那是个好节目。
- I heard it was a good show.
非常令人不安。多个的耳朵。
Very disturbing. Multiple ears.
哇。
Wow.
一定很好。
Got to be good.
这是好的。
It was okay.
如果你喜欢逃避现实的宣传。
If you like escapist propaganda.
有人跟我谈了我对内在美的看法。
This someone talked to me about my take on inner beauty.
他说我真的应该去看医生。
Said I really should consult with a doctor.
Nasatir博士。
Dr. Nasatir.
内在美,是吧?
Inner beauty, huh?
那正是你的拿手好戏。
That's right up your alley.
我猜这就是她找我的原因
- Guess that's why she was talking to me.
好的,很好。
Okay, good.
跟随它。
Follow it up.
看看这是什么意思。
Find out what it means.
还有什么?
What else?
-为什么你们的尸体犯罪小组叫新扫黄组?
- Why is your body-crime unit called New Vice?
我不明白什么是犯罪。
I don't get the vice part.
-局里有人觉得这比《进化错乱》更性感。
- Somebody in the Bureau thought it was sexier than Evolutionary Derangement.
更性感意味着更容易融资。
Sexier means easier funding.
还有别的事吗?
Anything else?
是的。
Yeah.
地铁监狱里有个叫Djuna Dotrice的女人。
You have a woman named Djuna Dotrice in the Metro Pen.
我们有什么?
We have?
《新Vice》有她吗?
New Vice has her?
-可能只是老凶案组她犯了谋杀罪。
- Probably just Old Homicide. She's in for murder.
杀了自己的孩子。
Murdered her own kid.
是的。
Yeah.
好吗?
Well?
-我要和她谈谈。
- I need to talk to her.
-萨克号最初是一个验尸官的石棺。
- The Sark was originally a coroners' autopsy sarcophagus.
当它在医疗行业过时后，它作为艺术家的用品重新焕发了生机。
When it went out of style in the medical profession, it took on new life as artists' supplies.
-我听说一些被改造成表演手术的Sarks被残忍地砍了，但这一个是由一个非常细腻的人改造的。
- I've heard that some of the Sarks that were modified for performance surgery have been really brutally hacked around, but this one was converted by someone with a very delicate touch.
它的形状很漂亮。
It's in beautiful shape.
-你的搭档呢?
- Where's your partner?
-索尔喜欢我做技术狗的工作。
- Saul likes me to do the techno dog work.
让我和自己的根保持联系。
Keeps me in touch with my roots.
-他怎么了?
- What happened to him?
-身体生长的东西。
- The body-growth thing.
-有名字吗?
- Is there a name for it?
加速进化综合症。
Accelerated Evolution Syndrome.
你的身体会变得很有创造力，会向你抛出很多新东西。
Your body gets very inventive and throws a lot of new stuff at you.
我猜它是想看看下一代能得到什么。
I guess it wants to see what sticks for the next generation.
-是的，但是…坦瑟不会放过任何东西的，对吧?
- Yeah, but, uh... Tenser's not letting anything stick, is he?
我的意思是……如果他把这些都扔掉就不会了。
I mean... not if he's getting rid of it all.
新的，改进的身体部位?
the new, improved body parts?
这是病态的。
It's pathological.
这是不健康的。
It's not healthy.
这是系统的崩溃。
It's a breakdown of the system.
有机体需要有组织。
An organism needs organisation.
否则，它只是设计师的癌症。
Otherwise, it's just designer cancer.
嘿,反复无常。
Hey, Caprice.
看看我们!
Check us out!
你认为吗?
Whaddya think?
我们在这里有表演的前途吗?
Do we got a future in performance here?
肯定。
Definitely.
扫罗紧张。
Saul Tenser.
进来吧。
Come on in.
这非常令人兴奋。
This is very exciting.
是吗?
Is it?
在这里见到你，就像晴天霹雳。
Seeing you here, is like a lightning bolt from the blue.
这给了你很大的打击，很有说服力。
It strikes you very hard and very convincingly.
让我帮你拿外套。
Let me take your coat.
-我还是戴着吧
- Uh, I prefer to keep it on.
我冷。
I get cold.
-如果你不介意染色的话
- If you don't mind staining.
求你了，跳上去，露出你的腹部。
Please, just hop up on there and expose your abdomen.
-跟我说说闪电的事。
- Tell me about the lightning bolt.
——索尔·坦瑟和内在美。
- Saul Tenser and the Inner Beauties.
这是天作之合。
It's a marriage made in heaven.
内心的美。
Inner Beauties.
我建议在这里安装开锁。
I propose to install the rip-lock here.
这将给您最大的访问权限。
This will give you maximum access.
访问什么?
Access to what?
我想我是来讨论我的政治问题的。
I believe I'm here to discuss my political problem.
-我不知道你有。
- I wasn't aware you had one.
我也不知道，但艾德丽安·伯索似乎认为我知道。
I wasn't either, but Adrienne Berceau seems to think I do.
哦,艾德丽安。
Oh, Adrienne.
她很引人注目。
She's so dramatic.
听……我，我只是个机械师。
Listen... Me, I'm just a mechanic.
我为未来安装门窗。
I install doors and windows into the future.
当你注册的时候，政治很快就会到来。
Politics will come soon, when you're registered.
注册吗?
Registered?
为了什么?
For what?
他自己都不知道。
He doesn't even know.
参加内心选美比赛。
For the Inner Beauty Pageant.
我相信你会是一个有力的竞争者。
I'm sure you'll be a contender.
-嗨。-嗨。
- Hi. - Hi.
-萨克号怎么样了?
- How's the Sark coming along?
我们LifeFormWare的朋友们非常…
- Our LifeFormWare friends are very...
我该怎么说呢?
How can I put it?
很好玩的。
Very playful.
嗯。
Huh.
这是好事吗?
Is that a good thing?
-他们爱死那台机器了
- They love it to death, that piece of machinery.
它们真的会在上面流口水。
They literally salivate on it.
他们不会伤害它的。
They won't hurt it.
嗯。
Huh.
哇。
Wow.
这是什么?
And what's this?
减少自己剃须吗?
Cut yourself shaving?
-我好像是参加内心选美比赛的选手。
- I seem to be a contestant in the Inner Beauty Pageant.
很守秘。
It's very hush-hush.
可能不太合法。
Might not be quite legal.
-你拖回家的东西。
- The things you drag home.
嗯。
Hm.
我要参加"最佳无功能原创管风琴"的评选。
I'm entering in the category of Best Original Organ With No Known Function.
这就像给内脏器官闪光者准备的雨衣。
This is like a raincoat for internal organ flashers.
哇。
Wow.
一个新的世界打开了。
A new world opens up.
嗯。
Hm.
等一下。
Wait a minute.
我们是不是被发现了…过时了吗?
Have we just been made, um... obsolete?
-不，当然不是
- No, of course not.
它只是一个功能性的东西。
It's just a functional thing.
这是一个带拉链的苍蝇;
It's a zippered fly;
这不是艺术，也不是感性的。
it's not art, It's not sensual.
此外，记住性爱就是手术。
Besides, remember what sex is surgery.
一个拉链代替不了我们的萨克。
A zipper can't replace our Sark.
我想她说，呃…“手术就是新的性爱。”
I think she said, uh... "Surgery is the new sex."
除此之外,
Besides,
——拉链……拥有自己的性感。
- zippers... - have their own sex appeal.
小心……不泄漏。
Careful... don't spill.
-他吃了一个塑料废纸篓。
- He ate a plastic wastepaper basket.
你会怎么做?
What would you do?
-我不会杀他的
- I wouldn't kill him.
一个小孩，我自己的儿子。
A little kid, my own son.
-但他不会是你自己的儿子
- But he wouldn't be your own son.
他都不是个小孩子了。
He wouldn't even be a little kid.
-他会是什么?
- What would he be?
一个生物。
A creature.
一个东西。
A thing.
是我丈夫发明来折磨我的。
A thing my husband invented to torment me.
-一个可以吃掉塑料废纸篓的东西。
- A thing that can eat a plastic wastepaper basket.
-吃它，享受它。
- Eat it and enjoy it.
只吃塑料和奇怪的合成材料。
And eat nothing but plastic and weird synthetic stuff.
他会把那块表拿去当午餐。
He would take that watch and he'd have it for lunch.
-他能消化塑料?
- He could digest plastic?
他有一种奇怪的、厚厚的白色流口水，他有时会对着一切东西发出啧啧声。
He had this weird, thick white drool that he'd sometimes slurp over everything.
就像酸一样。
It was like acid.
它能溶解任何塑料物质。
It'd dissolve any kind of plasticky stuff.
如果你把它弄到皮肤上就会刺痛。
It would sting if you got it on your skin.
但他没在意。
Didn't bother him, though.
蜥蜴。
That lizard.
-你丈夫是朗·多特里丝
- Your husband is Lang Dotrice.
是什么。
Was.
是我的丈夫。我和他断绝了关系——操他。
Was my husband. I've disowned him - fuck him.
-他发明了你的儿子?
- He invented your son?
是的。
Yeah.
这就是我的看法。
That's how I think of it.
还有一件事一想到在我体内生长的黏糊糊的虫子我就恶心。
And here's another thing the thought of that slimy worm growing in me still makes me sick.
警察告诉我他们还没找到你儿子布雷肯。
The police tell me they haven't found your son, Brecken.
我觉得他们不认为你真的杀了他。
I get the feeling they don't think you really killed him.
我承认他们不相信我。
I confess they don't believe me.
完美的犯罪。
The perfect crime.
你承认吗?
You confessed?
是的。
Yeah.
为什么?
Why?
我有罪。
I'm guilty.
身体在哪里?
Where's the body?
-朗拿走了，除非他把它扔了。
- Lang has it unless he's thrown it away.
-他怎么拿到的?
- How'd he get it?
-我留给他的
- I left it for him.
我的离婚小礼物。
My little divorce present.
-朗要怎么处理尸体?
- What is Lang going to do with the body?
-也许他和他的食人族朋友会吃掉它。
- Maybe him and his cannibal friends are going to eat it.
谁他妈知道?谁他妈在乎?
Who the fuck knows? Who the fuck cares?
-他的朋友都是食人族?
- His friends are cannibals?
——嗯。
- Um-hm.
如果你是芭比娃娃，那他们就是食人族。
If you're a Barbie Doll, then they're cannibals.
-如果警察找到布雷肯的尸体并进行尸检，你认为他们会在里面发现什么?
- If the police found Brecken's body and did an autopsy, what do you think they'd find inside it?
外太空。
Outer space.
——塔尔。——朗。
- Tarr. - Lang.
每个人都在这里。
Everybody's here.
好。
Good.
-我们的补给线又开始运行了，所以我们的状况很好。
- Our supply lines are up and running again, so we're in very good shape.
生产很快就会恢复到最高水平。
Production will soon be back to maximum.
-塔尔，如果我们要搬迁公社，我是说，整个运作，流水线，所有的一切…坐下。
- Tarr, if we have to move the commune, I mean, the whole operation, the assembly line, everything... Sit.
它能有多快?
How quickly can it be?
-你以为会有问题吗?
- You're expecting problems?
-我要继续做布雷肯的尸检。
- I'm going ahead with the Brecken autopsy.
最后，我们所做的将会是非常公开的，它将会引起共鸣。
Finally, what we're doing is going to be very public and it's going to resonate.
哦……
Oh...
哦。
Oh.
紧张先生在哪儿?
Where's Mr. Tenser?
-他在做一些研究。——啊。
- He's doing some research. - Ah.
-你的朋友蒂姆林呢?
- Where's your friend, Timlin?
-她被吓到了
- Oh, she was, uh, intimidated.
由谁?
By whom?
我们被禁止交往。
Well, we've been forbidden to mingle.
现在这是工作描述的一部分。
It's now part of the job description.
我来这里就拿我的职业生涯冒险，但是…我不能离开。
I'm risking my career just being here, but, uh... I can't stay away.
我发烧了。
I've got the fever.
原谅我。
Forgive me.
我得在她走之前跟她谈谈。
I've got to talk to her before she goes.
至理名言。
Odile.
反复无常。
Caprice.
你不知道我有多难找到能理解我不想变得更漂亮的整形医生。
Oh, you have no idea how hard it's been for me to find plastic surgeons who understand that I do not wish to be made more beautiful.
-外科医生往往非常专注，缺乏想象力。
- Surgeons tend to be very focussed and unimaginative.
这被认为是一种力量。
It's considered a strength.
我自己就是个外科医生。
I was a surgeon myself.
但不是整容手术。
Not cosmetic surgery, though.
——创伤。
- Trauma.
创伤。
Trauma.
但这是非常……挑衅。
But that's very um... provocative.
我喜欢创伤。
I enjoy trauma.
我对自己的所作所为让我深受创伤。
What I do to myself is very traumatic.
是吗?
Is it?
你看起来很平静，所以…在你做手术的时候感到幸福。
You seem so peaceful, so... beatific while your surgery's going on.
看你突然……我充满了想把脸割开的欲望。
Watching you suddenly... filled me with the desire to cut my face open.
这种感觉让我震惊。
It's a feeling that shocked me.
-对开放的渴望通常是令人兴奋的... ...新事物的开始。
- A desire to be open is often the beginning of something exciting... ...new.
也许你愿意今晚晚些时候和我以及剧团一起去酒店?
Perhaps you would like to join me and the troupe later this evening, at the hotel?
-想要敞开心扉?
- A desire to be open?
比喻。
Metaphorically.
的情绪。
Emotionally.
在艺术上。
Artistically.
-你想接管布雷肯的节目。
- You want to take over the Brecken show.
-我想做尸检。
- I want to perform the autopsy.
我想表演。
I want to perform.
-这是新的
- Well, this is new.
-是的。
- Yes, it is.
也许……你以前太害羞了。
Maybe... you were too shy before.
-我现在不太害羞了。
- I'm not too shy now.
你会为这个节目带来一些新的东西吗?
Will you have something new for the show?
我们完全可以用张紧器进行提取。
We could definitely do work in a Tenser extraction.
解剖的两倍。
Double Autopsy.
嗯。
Hm.
我确实做了点东西。
I do have something cooking.
也许有一些事情。
Maybe a few things.
但我很乐意让他们暂时待在屋里。
But I'm happy to let them stay inside for now.
-那可能不健康
- That might not be healthy.
-如果有问题，我们可以私下撤离。
- We can extract in private, if it's a problem.
不一定是表演。
Doesn't have to be a performance.
-不要拖太久。
- Don't let it go too long.
- Odile的表演怎么样?
- How was Odile's show?
这是……——聪明的。
It was... - Brilliant.
她是令人振奋的。
She's exhilarating.
是的。
Yeah.
-她说你好。
- She says hello.
你好。
Hello.
-我想做的不仅仅是表演。
- I want to do more than perform.
我想要构建。
I want to construct.
我想建造布雷肯秀。
I want to construct the Brecken show.
-它已经有了一个先天的结构。
- It already has an innate structure.
一个被谋杀的男孩。
A murdered boy.
一个非常奇怪的男孩。
A very strange boy.
公开尸检，一些…惊喜。
A public autopsy, some... surprises.
-我想和它合作。
- I want to work with it.
它充满了意义。
It's juicy with meaning.
扫罗紧张。
Saul Tenser.
好吧，那进来吧。
Well, then, come on in.
嗯。
Hm.
只是…
Just...
有什么事吗?
What's up?
哦,好吧…我只是想听听你对新器官制造者的建议。
Oh, well... I just want your advice as a neo-organ generator.
我…,就…嗯…事实上，我想带你看看我们的安全屋。
I... - just... Uh... actually, I wanted to show you our safe room.
我可以吗?
Can I?
是的……所以，这里是我们存放更刺激素材的地方。
Yes... So, this is where we archive our more provocative material in here.
-我认为这是挑衅。
- I thought it was all provocative.
你，你激怒了我们。
You, - you provoke us.
——嗯…你，你激怒了我。
- Uh... You, you provoke me.
我很高兴你能和我们在一起。
I'm-- I'm just so glad you're with us, you know.
这在情感上很有意义。
It makes such emotional sense.
我们是谁?
Who's us?
是我,我…我是一个。
It's me, I'm... I'm the one.
我是内心选美大赛的注册员。
I am the Registrar for the Inner Beauty Pageant.
-嘘，别告诉别人。
- Sh, don't tell.
登记似乎是你的强项。
Registration seems to be your strong suit.
-我觉得你很有可能赢得你的奖项。
- I-I think you have a very good chance of winning your category.
事实上，如果我是你，我会去争取最佳表演奖。
In fact, if I were you, I'd go for Best in Show.
-我不确定我能展示什么。
- I'm not sure I'll have anything to show.
可能得装出来。
Might have to fake it.
-说到假装，我说过和内在美在一起对你来说是有感情意义的，确实如此，但是…你知道，这不合逻辑。
- Speaking of faking it, I said it makes emotional sense for you to be with the Inner Beauties, and it does, but... you know, doesn't make logical sense.
——不是吗?——没有。
- No? - No.
-因为“内心选美”的核心是接受。
- Because the Inner Beauty Pageant is all about acceptance.
它是关于承认，审美的赋予，而你，索尔·坦瑟，你是关于愤怒，和反叛，和…拒绝了手术刀。
It's about acknowledgment, aesthetic empowerment, And you, Saul Tenser, you're all about anger, and rebellion, and... rejection by scalpel.
-这是个错误，不是吗?
- This has been a mistake, hasn't it?
不。
No.
-你说得对。在你的小秘密活动中我会感到很不自在。
- No, you're right. I'd be a fish out of water at your little secret event.
但是，不，不，不。
But, no, no, no.
我们想要你，我们需要你，我们…没有你，一切都会散架的!
We want you, we need you, we-we... It'll all fall apart without you!
-如果我赢得了最佳原创管风琴奖，然后在我下次演出的时候当众把它撕了呢?
- What if I won for best original organ and then I ripped it out in public at my next show?
那不会让你的团队蒙羞吗?
Wouldn't that humiliate your group?
明星效应。我们就就会覆盖它。
It's star power. We'll-we'll-we'll cover it.
我们会,我们会解决的。
We'll, we'll settle.
你想要什么我们都会给你也许，只是也许，你会开始以我们的方式看待这件事。
We'll give you whatever you want and maybe, just maybe, you'll begin to see it our way.
——嗯…-所以…好吧…我们倒带。
- Uh... - So-- So, okay... we rewind.
——我…我是来报名参加内心选美比赛的。
- I, uh... I'm here to register for the Inner Beauty Pageant.
——紧张先生吗?——啊!哦。
- Mr. Tenser? - Ah! Oh.
——扫罗……——这是你。
- Saul... - It's you.
你能到我办公室来一下吗?
- Could you come into my office?
你刚刚和威佩特先生在一起。
You were just with Mr. Wippet.
我是。
I was.
-我很担心他。
- I'm very worried about him.
-他看起来状态不错。
- He seemed to be in fine form.
-不，这是一种非常危险的形式。
- Oh, no, it's a very dangerous form to be in.
-我不明白
- I-- I don't understand.
……在我们这行，很容易被演艺圈的魅力所迷惑，
It's... in our line of work, very easy to be dazzled by the glamour of the performance world,
我们遇到的那些有魅力的人，比如你。
the charismatic people we meet, like you.
我明白了。
I see.
你呢?
Do you?
——也许不是。告诉我。
- Maybe not. Tell me.
-这是我们的世界
- Well, this is our world.
这间办公室，这栋大楼。
This office, this building.
从它的中心，在它的深处，这美丽的白光向外散发。
From the centre of it, deep, deep within it, this beautiful white light emanates outward.
那道光就是你，你所创造的，以及那些喜欢你的人。
That light is you, what you create, and those like you.
…我们这些乏味的官僚小昆虫，很难不被你强大的引力场所吸引。
Mm... It's hard-it's hard for us, drab little bureaucratic insects that we are, not to be drawn into your powerful gravitational field.
向你飞奔而来，坠入把所有光都吸进去的黑洞。
Hurtling towards you, plunging into your black hole that pulls all light into it.
我们想追随那道光，与那道光融合。
We want to follow that light, fuse with that light.
-威佩特在做熔合吗-你觉得呢
- Is-- Is Wippet doing some fusing, - do you think?
哦……他被内在美所吸引。
Oh... He's-he is drawn to inner beauty.
-他在和颠覆组织玩游戏吗?
- Is he playing games with subversive groups?
你是这个意思吗?
Is that-is that what you mean?
我…我非常非常喜欢他，但是……是啊，我想我可能得告发他了。
I... I am very, very fond of him, but... Yes, I think I might have to actually turn him in.
-不，别，别，别那样
- No, don't-don't-don't do that.
——嗯…
- Uh...
这个房间安全吗?
How safe is this room?
哦,这是……它是完全安全的。
Oh, it's... It's totally safe.
你可以对我坦白。
You can be open with me.
是的,打开。
Yeah, open.
嗯…你有没有遇到过一种新型的风琴……或者更确切地说，是一种具有消化功能的新器官系统?
Um... Have you run across a neo-organ... or rather, a system of neo-organs, that had a digestive function?
一个可以消化合成物、塑料……诸如此类的事情?
A system that can digest synthetics, plastics... that sort of thing?
不。
No.
没有，但听起来很有趣。
No, but that sounds interesting.
我们只遇到过单一器官的生长，比如你的。
We've only come across single organ growths here, like yours.
当然，没有人知道如果任由这些增长累积会发生什么。
Of course, nobody knows what would happen if those growths were allowed to accumulate.
你觉得他们能——呃，我差点说到进化，但我没有。哈。
Do you think they could ev-- Um, I almost said evolve, - but I didn't. Hah.
嗯…你认为他们真的能发展成……器官系统?
Um... Do you think they could actually develop into... a system of organs?
像一个…循环系统,
like a... circulatory system,
神经系统,嗯…淋巴……?
nervous system, um... lymphatic...?
-你对人体生理学很了解。
- You know a lot about human physiology.
是的。
Yeah.
——嗯。
- Hm.
-你觉得你会让我参加你的节目吗?
- Do you think you would ever let me be a part of your show?
嗯…因为我很想…发现自己在沙克舱里…你来控制。
Uh... Because I would love to... find myself in that Sark module with... you at the controls.
-这绝对是新Vice的范畴。
- That would, that would definitely fall into the category of New Vice.
…嗯，那就是我住的地方。
Mm... Well, that is where I live.
——嗯。
- Hm.
啊。
Ah.
-哦…嗯…
- Oh... Uh...
——我很抱歉。——没有。
- I'm sorry. - No.
-我只是不太擅长老炮友。
- I'm just not very good at the old sex.
-请进。
- Please, come in.
你喜欢坐哪坐哪。
Sit, uh, anywhere you like.
这是反复无常的。
This is Caprice.
她是我的伙伴。
She's my partner.
-是的，我看过你的作品。
- Yes, I've seen your work.
美丽。优秀的东西。
Beautiful. Outstanding stuff.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
-我和你妻子谈过了
- I spoke to your wife.
你的前妻。
Your ex-wife.
-你为什么这么做?
- Why'd you do that?
-我想知道我们在做什么。
- I wanted to know what we were getting into.
-你现在知道了吗?
- Do you know now?
不完全是。
Not exactly.
——好的。
- Okay.
-我们就从这个开始吧
- Why don't we, uh, start with this.
你不想看看你的原材料吗?
Don't you want to take a look at your raw materials?
请。
Please.
-我觉得我们不应该这么做。
- I don't think we should do this.
-也许你不应该这么做。
- Maybe you shouldn't.
-但你显然是想让我们这么做。
- But you obviously really want us to.
你为什么?
Why do you?
-我要发表声明。
- I need to make a statement.
一个非常公开的声明。
A very public statement.
嗯。
Hm.
正式的警方尸检难道不能说明这一点吗?
Wouldn't a formal police autopsy make that statement?
-不，不，会被盖起来的。
- No, no, it would be covered up.
你什么也听不到。
You'd never hear a thing.
-行为艺术都是两厢情愿的。
- Performance art is all consensual.
这次就不一样了。
This one would be different.
这将是不同的。
This would be different.
-是的，我会同意的。
- Yes, well, you'll have my consent.
Brecken不说话。
Brecken isn't talking.
我相信你知道狄娜不在乎她儿子的尸体会怎么样。
I'm sure you realize that Djuna doesn't care what happens to her son's body.
-我感觉她对他的身体很着迷。
- I got the feeling she was obsessed with his body.
尤其是他的消化系统。
Especially his digestive system.
——啊。嗯…
- Ah. Well...
吃过这个吗?
Ever eaten one of these?
-从没见过这种东西。
- Never seen one of those before.
——继续。请。
- Go ahead. Please.
我认为这将是一个启示。
I think it'll be a revelation.
-我对食物很挑剔。
- I'm very fussy about my food.
-是啊，我也是
- Yeah, so am I.
Brecken也是。
So was Brecken.
让我看看EatWare应用程序对你有用吗?
Let me does the EatWare application work for you?
我曾经在一个展厅的橱窗里看过LifeFormWare公司的BreakFaster椅子。
I looked at one of those BreakFaster chairs from LifeFormWare in a showroom window once.
它们调整你身体的每个部分，使咀嚼、吞咽和消化变得容易。
The way they adjust every part of your body to make chewing, swallowing and digesting easy.
在我生命中的某个时刻，我以为这可能就是答案。
At one point in my life I thought that might be the answer.
什么问题吗?
To what question?
我的饮食问题，布雷肯的…你确实做到了。
- The eating problem that I have, Brecken had... and that you have.
嗯。
Hm.
你觉得他们有关系?
You think they're related?
-你是一个在与真实的自己抗争的人。
- You're a man who's fighting what he really is.
你没有看见吗?
Don't you see?
你应该让你的身体引导你去它想去的地方，而不是把它砍成碎片，像灭绝动物的骨头一样在某个隐藏的博物馆里展示。
You should let your body lead you to where it wants to go instead of hacking it to pieces and displaying it in some hidden museum like the bones of an extinct animal.
-如果Saul听了这个建议，他现在已经死了。
- Saul would be dead now if he listened to that advice.
他的身体想要他的命。
His body wants to kill him.
我们所做的是在无政府状态下创造艺术。
What we're doing is we're making art out of anarchy.
我们在空虚中创造意义。
We are creating meaning out of emptiness.
是吗?
Are you?
你有没有想过，你可能只是在干扰一个你应该屈服的奇妙的自然过程?
Has it ever occurred to you that you might simply be interfering in a fantastic natural process that you should surrender to?
从来没有。
Never has.
你会参加布雷肯的节目吗?
Will you do the Brecken show?
-我应该做布雷肯的节目吗?
- Should I do the Brecken show?
新Vice想从中得到什么?
What does New Vice want to get out of this?
-你有了新闺蜜
- You have a new best friend.
-那是谁?
- Who would that be?
朗Dotrice。
Lang Dotrice.
我们想要他。
We want him.
但我们要的不仅仅是他。
But we don't just want him.
我们想要他那群怪胎。
We want his group of freaks.
他们所有人。
All of them.
-我不知道什么组织。
- I don't know anything about a group.
-你会了解这个团体的。
- You will find out about the group.
他喜欢你。
He likes you.
他信任你。
He trusts you.
-他信任我在公共场合肢解他死去的儿子。
- He trusts me to cut up his dead son in public.
我们会得到什么?
What'll that get us?
-它可以让你进入下一个阶段，即渗透。
- It could get you to the next stage, which is infiltration.
我们要知道关于多特丽丝和他那些吃塑料的战友们的一切。
We want to know everything there is to know about Dotrice and his plastic-eating comrades.
——Plastic-eating ?
- Plastic-eating?
-你还不明白?
- You don't get it yet?
-你说的是那些紫色的糖果?
- You talking about those purple candy bars?
-吃过吗?
- Ever try eating one of those?
我们的一个探员做到了。
One of our agents did.
他现在和布雷肯一样死了。
He's as dead as Brecken now.
毒害了他吗?
Poisoned him?
他们synth酒吧。
They're synth bars.
合成的,人造的东西。
Synthetic, man-made stuff.
有毒的。
Toxic.
正常人不能吃那种东西。
A normal human can't eat that stuff.
但那些人-他们只是…它们只是不停地咀嚼，没有问题。
But those people, - they just... they just munch away, no problem.
他们正在远离人类的道路，索尔。
They're evolving away from the human path, Saul.
不能让这种情况继续下去。
It can't be allowed to continue.
医生Nasatir吗?
Doctor Nasatir?
是吗?
Yes?
-路由器和Berst的LifeFormWare。
- Router and Berst of LifeFormWare.
授权的技术人员。
Authorized technicians.
你打电话给我们，我们来了。
You called us, we're here.
我给你打电话了吗?
Did I call you?
-改变你的早餐椅模式。
- A paradigm shift with your BreakFaster chair.
-没错，但我现在正在吃饭。
- Yes, that's true, but I'm just eating now.
哦，来得正是时候。
Oh, it's perfect timing.
-我们要把所有东西都搬走。
- We're moving everything out.
这位塔尔先生，他负责一切。
Mr. Tarr here, he's taking care of everything.
我觉得布雷肯的节目会让我们变得很性感，但这个，
I figure the Brecken show is going to make us too hot but this,
我们都吃这个。
this is what all of us eat.
-我们所有人，是多少?
- All of us, is how many?
-嗯，我们自己的小细胞，有六七十个人，但在世界各地，我们的网络是巨大的。
- Well, our own little cell, 60, 70 souls but around the world, our network is vast.
实际上，这个数字是不可知的。
And, really, the number's unknowable.
-每个人都做过同样复杂的手术吗?
- And everybody's had the same elaborate surgery?
塔尔。
Tarr.
世界上的每个人，是的。
Everyone around the world, yes.
这些程序是多年合作开发出来的。
The procedures were developed over years of collaboration.
当然，也有不同的情况。
There are variations, of course.
文化独特的版本。
Culturally unique versions.
-你这么做是因为?
- And you did it because?
-因为我们的身体告诉我们是时候改变了，是吗?
- Because our bodies were telling us it was time to change, yes?
是时候让人类进化与人类科技同步了。
Time for human evolution to sync up with human technology.
我们必须开始以我们自己的工业废料为食。
We've got to start feeding on our own industrial waste.
这是我们的命运。
It's our destiny.
-最终的结果是你不能吃食物。
- The end result is you can't eat food.
-我们吃的是现代食物。
- Well, we eat modern food.
我们吃塑料。
We eat plastic.
我们喜欢这样称呼它。
And that's what we like to call it.
和Brecken吗?
And Brecken?
Brecken。
Brecken.
布雷肯是长子。
Brecken was the first-born.
-第一个生来就有塑料的…处理消化系统。
- The first to be born with a plastic... processing digestive system.
…自然不自然。
To be... naturally unnatural.
-她恨我们。Djuna恨我们。
- She hated us. Djuna hated us.
她从我们身边偷走了布雷肯。
She stole Brecken away from us.
她从来没有真正明白她的孩子是一个多么宝贵的人。
She never really understood what a gem her kid was.
她，她无法接受。
She-- she couldn't handle it.
-他一定是个了不起的人，因为你说的话听起来很疯狂。
- He really must have been a gem, because what you're saying sounds insane to me.
为什么?
Why?
-你是说你的手术，那个让你吃塑料的手术，
- Well, you're saying your surgery, the surgery that made you plastic eaters,
从基因上复制到你儿子身上了吗?
was somehow replicated genetically in your son?
通过手术获得的特征是可以遗传的?
That surgically acquired characteristics became inheritable?
你切掉了自己的小手指，而你的孩子生来就没有小手指?
You cut off your little finger and your kids are born without little fingers?
-布雷肯是我们的奇迹孩子。
- Brecken was our miracle child.
他是我们梦寐以求的那种人。
He was everything we all wanted to be.
这就是我能说的。
That's all I can say.
我不能说我理解这个过程。
Can't say I understand the process.
-但为什么是布雷肯的节目?
- But why a Brecken show?
-因为我想有一天，向全世界展示我的儿子。
- Because I wanted to, someday, present my son to the world.
我想向世界展示人类的未来是存在的，是美好的。
I wanted to show the world that the future of humanity existed and was good.
与我们所创造的科技世界保持着和平与和谐。
Was at peace and harmony with the techno world that we've created.
现在，我所能做的就是把他那小小的尸体呈现出来作为对未来的承诺。
Now, all I can do is present the reality of his dead little body as a promise of that future.
我不知道我们会看到什么。
I don't know what we'll see.
但我知道他会很漂亮。
But I know he'll be beautiful.
甜美、真实、美丽。
Sweet and real and beautiful.
对不起,我要……
Sorry, I gotta...
我没想到你会在这里。
I didn't expect you to be here.
——嗯。-就是躲不开，是吧?
- Hm. - Couldn't keep away, huh?
猜不是。
Guess not.
特殊的事件。
Special event.
-嗯嗯。
- Mm-hm.
值得冒这个风险。
Worth the risk.
-我们都想看尸检，不是吗?
- We've all wanted to see an autopsy, haven't we?
我们都觉得身体是空的，没有意义，我们想确认这一点，这样我们就能让它充满意义。
We've all felt that the body was empty, empty of meaning and we've wanted to confirm that, so that we could fill it with meaning.
Autopsia是指亲眼看到。
Autopsia means the seeing for oneself.
为什么第一次尸检吗?
Why First Autopsy?
因为我们知道还会有第二次尸检。
Because we know there'll have to be a Second Autopsy.
如果你想做尸检，你需要一具尸体。
If you want to do an autopsy, you need a corpse.
肉体的结合,肥胖的。
Corporeal, incorporate, corpulent.
身体语言。
Body words.
的单词。
Fleshy words.
布雷肯是我们的尸体。
Brecken is our corpse.
布雷肯是一个小男孩，他被他的母亲谋杀，因为他体内隐藏的东西。
Brecken was a young boy who was murdered by his mother because of what was hidden in his body.
因为那是有意义的。
Because of the meaning that was there.
对她来说，身体并非毫无意义。
For her, the body was not empty of meaning.
现在让我们深入布雷肯的身体，像文学教授一样，寻找隐藏在布雷肯这首诗中的意义。
And now let us dive deep into the body of Brecken and, like professors of literature, search for the meaning that lies locked in the poem that was Brecken.
哦,我的上帝。
Oh, my God.
哦。
Oh.
所以，我们看到这个世界的粗俗、绝望和丑陋已经渗透到我们最年轻、最美丽的内心。
So, we see that the crudeness and the desperation and the ugliness of the world has seeped inside even our youngest and most beautiful.
我们看到这个世界正在从内到外杀死我们的孩子。
And we see that the world is killing our children from the inside out.
这是今天的病理解剖。
Here we have the anatomy of today's pathology.
现在我们知道为什么要进行第二次和第三次尸检了。
And we know now why we'll have a Second Autopsy, and a Third.
我们知道我们必须保持…回到内心深处，希望能找到不同的答案。
We know that we'll have to keep... diving back deep inside, hoping to find a different answer.
但今晚，让我们不要害怕描绘出内心的混乱。
But for tonight, let us not be afraid to map the chaos inside.
让我们创造一张地图指引我们进入黑暗的中心。
Let us create a map that will guide us into the heart of darkness.
不,不,不。
No, no, no.
不，不，不，不。
No, no, no, no, no, no.
-太可怕了。
- That was hideous.
-我感觉糟透了。
- I feel so awful.
-他在里面不是那样的，他不是那样的。
- That's not what he was inside, that's not what he was.
她这样做。
She did this.
——她?-她她她
- She? - She, she, she.
——前妻;尸体的母亲。
- The ex-wife; the mother of the cadaver.
Djuna吗?
Djuna?
不,她没有。
No, she didn't.
她跟这事一点关系都没有。
She had nothing to do with it.
-她当然说了
- Of course she did.
你在里面看到的，是她给我的信息，给我的。
What you saw in there, that was her message to me, to me.
-不，不是。
- No, it wasn't.
不过我觉得她会同意的。
I have a feeling she'd approve of this, though.
-抱歉我迟到了。
- I'm sorry I'm late.
最近有很多会议。
Lots of meetings these days.
嗯……新Vice越来越大了，是吧?
Hm... New Vice is getting quite big, is it?
这是现在。
It is now.
很多人都被吓到了。
A lot of people running scared.
这么多吃塑料的人拿着手术刀到处跑。
So many plastic-eaters running around with scalpels.
让人没有安全感。
Makes people insecure.
-那些吃塑料的人很会用手术刀。
- They're pretty good with the scalpels, those plastic-eaters.
比那个黑布雷肯的人强多了。
Better than whoever did that hack job on Brecken's insides.
——是的,所以…好吧……好了，里面有个人。
- Yeah, so... Okay... Okay, we've got a man inside.
我们先到的。
We got there first.
那孩子的内心很奇怪。
The kid was pretty weird inside anyway.
你可能什么都认不出来，但最糟糕的是……这一切都是自然的。
You wouldn't have recognized a thing, but the hell of it was that... it was all natural.
他生来如此。
He was born that way.
-你不会想让所有人都知道的。
- You wouldn't want everybody to know that.
我不能。
I couldn't.
我不能泄露出去。
I couldn't let that out.
一旦它从盒子里拿出来，你就再也放不回去了。
Once that got out of the box, you would never be able to put it back in.
是你在登记处的朋友干的。
Your friend at the Registry did the work.
“灵感来自任性。”
"Inspired by Caprice."
我的朋友吗?
My friend?
你的意思是,Wippet ?
You mean, Wippet?
-不，那个奇怪的小女人
- No, that strange little woman.
-她叫什么名字?
- What's her name?
嗯,Timlin。
Uh, Timlin.
-我想知道她来表演做什么。
- I wondered what she was doing at the show.
我猜她是忍不住要看看她的作品。
I guess she couldn't resist checking out her work.
-她真的很想为你做Caprice，如果你明白我的意思。
- She really wants to be Caprice for you, if you know what I mean.
我知道你知道。
And I know that you do.
-那Dotrice的暗杀呢?
- And Dotrice's assassination?
暗杀?
Assassination?
谋杀的华丽词儿。
Fancy word for murder.
-他是个领袖。
- He was a leader.
他是有原因的。
He had a cause.
-不管是什么，对我来说也是个惊喜。
- Whatever it was, it was a surprise to me too.
-你有个不告诉我事情的坏习惯。
- You have a bad habit of not telling me things.
这使得它很难发挥作用。
It makes it difficult to function.
-我告诉你，我们不知道。
- I'm telling you, we didn't know about it.
也许……也许是他的疯老婆影响了他。
Maybe... Maybe his crazy wife got to him somehow.
我不知道。
I don't know.
不,不,不。
No, no, no.
谁杀了他并不重要。
Well, it doesn't matter who killed him.
这会让他成为殉道者。
It's going to make him a martyr.
正是这个事业所需要的。
Just what the cause needs.
的原因吗?
The cause?
听起来你正在成为一个信徒。
Sounds like you are becoming a believer.
-如果你想要擅长卧底生活，你必须有一部分信仰。
- If you're going to be good at living undercover, a part of you has to believe.
扫罗!
Saul!
哦……
Oh...
哦!
Uh!
嗯,嗯。
Uh, uh-uh.
-你很痛苦。
- You are in pain.
嗯…
Uh...
是我吗?
Was I?
是什么样的?
What's it like?
身体疼痛吗?
Physical pain?
是的。
Yes.
-这很难弄清楚。
- It's hard to be clear about it.
它变成了……梦想的一部分。
It becomes... part of the dreaming.
夹杂着做梦时的情感痛苦，所以…
mixes with the emotional pain of the dreaming, so it's-it's...
这是困惑。
It's confused.
我…我几乎以为……我差点以为我…我是感觉。
I... I almost thought... I almost thought I was... I was feeling.
啊。
Ah.
啊…
Ahh...
-你梦到Dotrice了吗?
- Did you dream about Dotrice?
Dotrice……Djuna Brecken。
Dotrice... Djuna and Brecken.
他们都在萨克号上。
They were all in the Sark together.
一个家庭解剖。
A family autopsy.
-是谁控制的?
- Who was at the controls?
你。
You.
和我。
And I.
我们都是。
We both were.
扫罗…你觉得呢?
Well, Saul... what do you think?
——是的。我想是的。
- Yes. I think yes.
是时候试试了。
It's time to try it.